(Sheldon:)Okay. Enough chitchat.
Okay, step one: Locate your emergency key
to our apartment.
Step two: Enter our apartment.
Step three...
(Sheldon:)Enter my bedroom.
SHELDON: Step four...
- Yeah, hang on, getting another call.
(Sheldon:)No!
(Sheldon:)Let me tell you something. Personal
robots cannot get here soon enough.
(Raj:)And that bright little star
peeking her head out early today...
(Raj:)...that's Venus.
(Summer:)That is so cool.
You know a lot about space.
(Raj:)Come on. When you were on TV in Firefly,
you were actually in space.
(Summer:)You're not one of those guys
who believe that?
(Raj:)You mean one of the hopeless geeks?
No.
(Raj:)Those are crazy people.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
(Raj:)Howard, be a dear
and get me another one of these.